This is a placeholder file

INSTRUCTIONS FOR ADDING ST.PNG FAVICON:

1. Take the ST.png image you showed in the conversation
2. Save it to your computer
3. Copy it to this location: C:\Developer\portfolio\public\ST.png
4. Delete this placeholder file

The Next.js configuration has been updated to use ST.png as the favicon.
After adding the image file, your favicon will automatically update when you restart your development server or deploy your site.
